Marjorie Yang

Undergraduate Student

Expected Completion: December 2023

Solutions-oriented undergraduate student with a passion for the intersections between design, technology, and social impact. Proven track record in a diverse range of experience in design and media, delivering value in leadership, diligence, problem-solving, and her extensive set of technical skills as well.

Experience

2022-10 -Present

Web Designer & Developer (Part-time)

Covid-19 Impact Project, NYU Tisch

- Conduct user experience research on the current site.
- Plan an appropriate redesign based on the research using wireframes, sitemaps, and prototypes built on Figma.
- Work with content and media asset producers to build the redesigned site using WordPress.

2022-03 -2022-12

Networks Assistant (Part-time)

SiteSeers Team, NYU Tisch - ITP Department

- Worked with a team to develop websites for the ITP department using WordPress.
- Assisted with design ideation and implementation using Figma.
- Implemented improvements for accessibility on different projects.

2022-06 -2022-10

Creative Director, Researcher, and Developer

Rising - Immersive Game Installation, NYU Grant

- · Designed the game's UI using Figma.
- Developed and designed game interactivity using Unity, Adobe mixamo, and Python.

2019-07 -2019-08

Graphic Design Intern

Hengdu Law Firm (Beijing, China)

- Designed print materials such as brochures that are used for conventions in the US.
- · Assisted in translating marketing materials.
- Designed potential logos and corresponding merchandise packages.

Education

2020-09 -2023-12

BFA in Interactive Media Arts (3.8 GPA)

New York University, Tisch School of the Arts Minors: Computer Science & Environmental Studies Honors & Awards: Dean's List (past 2 years); *This Is

Not A Drill* Research Grant

2016-09 -2020-06

International Baccaulaureate Diploma

Dulwich College Beijing, High School

Honors & Awards: Pearson GCSE Highest Mark in China for Art & Design; Community Prefect; Graeme Salte Award for Innovation; Pioneering Spirit Grant

Personal Info

Address 429 E 6th St New York, NY 10009

Phone

+1 (646) 206-4434

Email

my2211@nyu.edu

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ marjorie-yang-000/

Skills

- + Visual Design
- + Interface Design
- + Front-End Development
- + Sitemap and Wireframing
- + User Stories
- + Communication
- + Leadership

Languages:

- + English
- + Chinese (Mandarin)

Volunteer Work

Co-founder of GuangAi Hope Project (Beijing, China) 2019 Supplied the understaffed

GuangAi elementary school with student volunteers.

Volunteer in New Hope Orphanage (Beijing, China) 2016-2019

Conferences